A Guide to the Thomas N. Downing Papers, 1947-1977
Library of Virginia
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 188)
  - Legislation Not Enacted, 2nd Session.
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries.
    - College of William and Mary--275th Anniversary (H. Con. Res. 615)
  - Master Files.
    - 1st Session, A-H (8 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 189)
  - Master Files.
    - 1st Session, I-Z (17 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 190)
  - Master Files.
    - 2nd Session, A-L (12 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 191)
  - Master Files.
    - 2nd Session, Mc-Z [X omitted] (14 folders)
  - Office Accounts.
    - Stationery
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 192)
  - Office Accounts.
    - Out-of-District Telephone Service, 1st-4th Qtrs 1968 (4 folders)
    - Telephone and Telegraph Bills (3 folders)
    - Flags
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 193)
  - Office Accounts.
    - Office Supplies and Services
    - Vouchers for District Office Expenses
  - Political Files, various dates.
    - Accomplishments--Bills Introduced, Bills Voted On
    - A
    - Campaign for TND, 1961-1966 (4 folders)
    - Congratulatory and Thank You Letter, 1964 and 1966
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 194)
  - Political Files, various dates.
    - Petitions, 1966
    - Campaign for TND, 1967-1968
    - Contributions, n.d.
    - Contributions and Expenditures
    - Campaigns (not TND), 1967-1968
    - Campaign Help, Fall 1968
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 195)
  - Political Files, various dates.
    - Contributions--Yearly
    - Campaign Contributions--30 September 1968, Reception
    - Campaign Materials and Services (2 folders)
    - Campaign Procedure
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 196)
  - Political Files, various dates.
    - Congratulatory Letters on Reelection, 1968 (2 folders)
    - Thank You Letters for Campaign Helpers (2 folders)
    - State Democratic Convention 27 July 1968
    - National Convention, 1968
    - State Democratic Central Committee
    - Democratic National Committee
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 197)
  - Political Files, various dates.
    - District Democratic Committee
    - D
    - Election Results, 1968
    - Rev. J. Cornelius Fauntleroy
    - Ferguson, William F., Jr., Campaign
    - Gubernatorial Campaign, 1968 (2 folders)
    - Reaction to Governor's Race, 19 November 1968
    - H, I (2 folders)
    - Jefferson-Jackson Day, Richmond, 1967-1968
    - Lists of People
    - Campaign Lists--Not Complete, 1968
    - Mailing Lists--Attorneys
    - Mailing Lists--Teachers in District
    - Zinc Newspaper Plate Photo--TND
    - Petitions of the Opposition, November 1968
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 198)
  - Political Files, various dates.
    - Petitions
    - Presidential Campaign, 1968
    - State Board of Elections Material
    - James F. Stafford--Campaign Opponent, 1968
    - T, V [U, X-Z omitted] (2 folders)
  - Post Office and Postmaster Materials, 89th-90th Congresses.
    - Accomac Postmastership
    - A
    - Belle Haven Postmastership
    - Bridgetown Post Office and Postmastership
    - B
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 199)
  - Post Office and Postmaster Materials, 89th-90th Congresses.
    - Cape Charles Post Office
    - Capeville Post Office
    - Cheriton Postmastership
    - Cobbs Creek Postmaster
    - C (2 folders)
    - Davis Wharf Post Office
    - Deltaville Postmaster
    - D-F (3 folders)
    - Greenbackville Postmaster
    - Gwynn Post Office
    - G
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 200)
  - Post Office and Postmaster Materials, 89th-90th Congresses.
    - Hallwood Postmaster
    - Hayes Postmastership
    - Hayes Rural Carrier No. 2
    - Hampton Post Office
    - Hampton-Newport News
    - H
    - Justisville
    - J, K (2 folders)
    - Lightfoot Postmaster
    - Lynnhaven Post Office
    - L
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 201)
  - Post Office and Postmaster Materials, 89th-90th Congresses.
    - Mappsville Post Office
    - Melfa Post Office
    - M
    - New Kent Rural Carrier
    - Newport News Post Office
    - Newport News Rural Route One
    - N
    - Onancock
    - Onley
    - O
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 202)
  - Post Office and Postmaster Materials, 89th-90th Congresses.
    - Painter Post Office
    - Port Haywood Post Office
    - Postmaster and Post Office--General
    - Princess Anne Postmastership
    - Providence Forge Rural Route
    - P
    - Remlik Post Office
    - Rural Routes
    - R
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 203)
  - Post Office and Postmaster Materials, 89th-90th Congresses.
    - Saluda Post Office
    - Seaford Post Office
    - Seaview Postmaster
    - Self-Service Post Offices
    - Star Routes
    - Syringa Post Office
    - S
    - Tangier Island Post Office
    - Toano Postmastership
    - Topping Postmaster
    - Tunstall Post Office
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 204)
  - Post Office and Postmaster Materials, 89th-90th Congresses.
    - T, U (2 folders)
    - Virginia Beach Postmaster and Post Office (2 folders)
    - Walkerton Postmaster and Post Office (2 folders)
    - Williamsburg Post Office
    - Williamsburg Rural Carrier
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 205)
  - Post Office and Postmaster Materials, 89th-90th Congresses.
    - W
    - Yorktown Postmaster
    - Y
  - Rivers and Harbors Material, 86th-90th Congresses.
    - Aberdeen Creek
    - Appropriations
    - Army Corps of Engineers
    - Assateague Channel
    - Authorizations
    - Back River--York County--Front Cove
    - Beach Creek
    - Bennetts Creek (2 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 206)
  - Rivers and Harbors Material, 86th-90th Congresses.
    - Bogue Bay
    - Broad Creek--Middlesex
    - Browns Bay
    - Burtons Bay
    - Cape Charles Harbor
    - Chesapeake Bay to Chincoteague
    - Chesconnessex Creek
    - Chickahominy River
    - Chisman Creek
    - Davis Creek
    - Deep Creek--Accomack
    - Deep Creek--Warwick
    - Deep Creek--Warwick Yacht and Country Club
    - Dismal Swamp Canal
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 207)
  - Rivers and Harbors Material, 86th-90th Congresses.
    - Dyers Creek
    - Elizabeth River
    - Federal Flood Insurance
    - Finney's Creek
    - Fisher's Creek--Newport News
    - Floyd Bay
    - Garden Creek
    - Rivers and Harbors--General (2 folders)
    - Goodwin Island (2 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 208)
  - Rivers and Harbors Material, 86th-90th Congresses.
    - Greenbackville Channel
    - Guilford Creek
    - Hampton Creek
    - Hampton Roads Improvements--Deepening of Channel
    - Holden's Creek
    - Horn Harbor
    - Hoskins Creek
    - Hurricane Damage--Eastern Shore
    - Hurricane Survey
    - Indian Creek
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 209)
  - Rivers and Harbors Material, 86th-90th Congresses.
    - Inland Waterway--Chesapeake Bay to Chincoteague Bay (2 folders)
    - Intracoastal Waterway
    - James River
    - James River Channel
    - Jamestown Seawall
    - Joint Inland Water Way Resolution
    - Kegotank Bay
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 210)
  - Rivers and Harbors Material, 86th-90th Congresses.
    - Kings Creek (2 folders)
    - Lake Erie-Ohio River Canal
    - Compilation of River and Harbor Laws
    - Little Boat Harbor
    - Little Creek
    - Little Creek--Princess Anne County
    - Long Creek
    - Lynnhaven Inlet and Bay (4 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 211)
  - Rivers and Harbors Material, 86th-90th Congresses.
    - Lynnhaven Inlet and Bay (2 folders)
    - Lynnhaven, Linkhorn and Broad Bays
    - Mattaponi River
    - McKanes Bay
    - Meachim's Creek
    - Metompkin Bay
    - Morris Island Bridge
    - Nandua Creek
    - Nansemond River
    - Nassawaddox Creek--Northampton County
    - Newmarket Creek
    - Newport News to Old Point--Channel--Norfolk Harbor
    - Newport News Flood Control
    - Norfolk District Engineer Office
    - North Channel
    - Occohannock Creek
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 212)
  - Rivers and Harbors Material, 86th-90th Congresses.
    - Onancock River
    - Oregon Inlet, N.C.
    - Oyster Channel (2 folders)
    - Pamunkey River (2 folders)
    - Parker's Creek
    - Parrott's Creek
    - Perrin River
    - Piankitank River
    - Pocomoke River (2 folders)
    - Poquoson River
    - Potomac River Basin
    - Powhatan Creek
    - Powell's Bay--Accomack
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 213)
  - Rivers and Harbors Material, 86th-90th Congresses.
    - Put-in Creek
    - Queens Creek--York County (2 folders)
    - Quinby Creek (2 folders)
    - Rappahannock River (2 folders)
    - Richmond Harbor
    - Rollinson Channel, Hatteras, N.C.
    - Rudee Inlet
    - Salem Church Dam
    - Salters Creek
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 214)
  - Rivers and Harbors Material, 86th-90th Congresses.
    - Smallers Drain
    - Smith Island
    - Saxis Island--Starling Creek (2 folders)
    - Sturgeon Creek
    - Swash Bay
    - Tangier Island
    - Taylor Creek
    - Thimble Shoal Channel
    - Urbanna Creek (3 folders)
    - Urbanna Creek Jetty
    - Virginia Beach
    - Virginian Bridge--Elizabeth River
    - Webb Island
    - Whiting Creek
    - Willoughby Bay
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 215)
  - Rivers and Harbors Material, 86th-90th Congresses.
    - Windmill Point Creek
    - Winter Harbor (2 folders)
    - Wishart's Point
    - York River
    - York and Pamunkey River
    - Young Creek
  - Speech Files and Press Releases.
    - American Merchan Marine Conference, 1967
    - Campaign Speeches (2 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 216)
  - Speech Files and Press Releases.
    - Commencement Addresses (2 folders)
    - Education and Labor Speeches
    - Extension of Remarks (2 folders)
    - Humorous Speeches
    - Introductions and Dedications
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 217)
  - Speech Files and Press Releases.
    - Patriotic Speeches (2 folders)
    - U.S. Government Speeches (2 folders)
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 218)
  - Speech Files and Press Releases.
    - Speeches--Miscellaneous Topics
    - Speeches--General, 1968
    - Press Releases
- 90th Congress, 1967-1968. (Box 219)
  - Voting Record, 90th Congress.
    - 1st and 2nd Sessions (2 folders)
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 219)
  - [Military] Academies.
    Note: Military Academy files contain student records and are therefore restricted in accordance with the Privacy Act. They may not be served.
    - Nominees to the Academies Entering in 1969 (2 folders)
    - Nominees that have Withdrawn
    - U.S. Air Force Academy Entering in 1969
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 220)
  - [Military] Academies.
    - U.S. Coast Guard Academy [1969]
    - U.S. Merchant Marine Academy Entering in 1969
    - U.S. Military Academy Entering in 1969
    - U.S. Naval Academy Entering 1969
    - Naval Academy Regrets for the Class Entering in 1970
    - Service Academies for Class of 1969
    - Military Academies, Class of 1970
    - Class Entering in 1970, Alcock-Eason (15 envelopes)
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 221)
  - [Military] Academies.
    - Class Entering in 1970--Foley-Weyant (44 envelopes)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Agriculture Committee (2 folders)
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 222)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Agricultural Conservation Program
    - Appropriations Committee (2 folders)
    - Appropriations Committee--Bankhead-Jones
    - Appropriations Committee--Coast Guard Reserve
    - Appropriations Committee--Farm Subsidy--$20,000 Limitation
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 223)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Appropriations Committee--HEW Appropriations
    - Appropriations Committee--HEW Appropriations--President's Veto
    - Appropriations Committee--HEW Labor Appropriations--House Vote to Override President's Veto
    - Appropriations Committee--Military Construction (H.R. 17970)
    - Appropriations Committee--OEO Appropriations
    - Appropriations Committee--Public Works--Sewage Treatment Construction, FY 1971
    - Appropriations Committee--Public Works--Craney Island Water Pollution
    - Appropriations Committee--Space Appropriations, FY 1971
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 224)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Appropriations Committee--National Timber Supply
    - Appropriations Committee--Department of Transportation--SST
    - Appropriations Committee--Vocational Education Amendments of 1968
    - Armed Services Committee (1 folder)
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 225)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Armed Services Committee (1 folder)
    - Armed Services Committee--ABM Missile System--Safeguard
    - Armed Services Committee--Draft, Including all Volunteer
    - Armed Services Committee--Aircraft Carrier--Military Procurement Authorization (H.R. 14000)
    - Armed Services Committee--Pueblo Inquiry--CDR Bucher
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 226)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Banking and Currency Committee
    - Banking and Currency Committee--8 1/2% Interest Increase
    - Banking and Currency Committee--Bank Holding Act
    - Banking and Currency Committee--One-Bank Holding Company
    - Committee Assignments
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 227)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Select Committee on Crime
    - Democratic Study Group
    - District of Columbia Committee
    - Education and Labor Committee (3 folders)
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 228)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Education and Labor Committee--Manpower Training
    - Education and Labor Committee--Occupational Safety (H.R. 12634 [8e]) (2 folders)
    - Education and Labor Committee--National Library Commission Act
    - Education and Labor Committee--Situs Picketing (H.R. 100)
    - Joint Committee on Economics
    - Foreign Affairs Committee (2 folders)
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 229)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Foreign Affairs--Cambodia
    - Foreign Affairs--Cambodia--Special File
    - Foreign Affairs--Israel--Jets--Letter to the President, 1970
    - Legislation--General (3 folders)
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 230)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Legislation--General (4 folders)
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 231)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Legislation--General (2 folders)
    - Major Legislative Actions, through 8 August 1969
    - Government Operations
    - Government Operations--Reorganization Plan #2
    - House Administration
    - Interior and Insula Affairs
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 232)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Interior and Insular Affairs--Archeological
    - Internal Security--General
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce (4 folders)
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 233)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce (2 folders)
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Clean Air Act Amendments
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Consumer Protection
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce--Hosmer Bill--Food Supplements and Vitamins (H.R. 1180)
    - Pay TV--FCC Proposal
    - Supplemental Railroad Annuities
    - Water Carrier Mixing Rule
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 234)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Judiciary Committee (2 folders)
    - Judiciary Committee--Bussing [sic]
    - Judiciary Committee--Dirksen Anti-Obscenity Bill (S. 1077)
    - Judiciary Committee--Electoral College (2 folders)
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 235)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Judiciary Committee--Honoring Captain John Fitch
    - Judiciary Committee--Martin Luther King National Holiday
    - Judiciary Committee--Omnibus Crime Control and Safe Streets Act
    - Judiciary Committee--Adam Clayton Powell
    - Judiciary Committee--Prayer Amendment Correspondence--A-Z (4 folders)
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 236)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Judiciary Committee--Prayers in Public
    - Judiciary Committee--Prayers--Whitehurst Referred
    - Judiciary Committee--Voting Reform
    - Judiciary Committee--Voting Rights Act of 1965
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee.
      - Conference on Maritime Bill (H.R. 15424)--Merchant Marine Act of 1936
      - Merchant Marine Act, 1936--Repeal 6% Differential (1 folder)
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 237)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee.
      - Merchant Marine Act, 1936--Repeal 6% Differential (5 folders)
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 238)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee.
      - Merchant Marine Act, 1936--Repeal 6% Differential (1 folder)
    - Special Committee on Parking
    - Post Office and Civil Service (3 folders)
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 239)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Post Office and Civil Service--Census
    - Post Office and Civil Service--Dual Compensation
    - Post Office and Civil Service--Government Employee Health Benefits Program
    - Post Office and Civil Service--Post Office Committee (H.R. 12823)
    - Post Office and Civil Service--Salary Increase--President's
    - Post Office and Civil Service--Blue Collar Pay Raise
    - Post Office and Civil Service--Letter Carrier Pay Increase
    - Post Office and Civil Service--Increase Retirement Annuities
    - Post Office and Civil Service--Compulsory Unionization
    - Post Office and Civil Service--Wage Board
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 240)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Post Office and Civil Service--Post Office Department--Kappel Report--Postal Reform
    - Post Office and Civil Service--Retirement (H.R. 9825)
    - Post Office and Civil Service--Postal Reorganization
    - Public Works Committee
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 241)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Public Works Committee--Disaster Loan
    - Public Works Committee--Water Quality Improvement Act of 1969
    - Public Works Committee--Highway Bill (H.R. 16788)
    - Public Works Committee--Grass Roots Trust Fund Approach
    - Public Works Committee--Trucking
    - Public Works Committee--Student Requests--Pollution
    - Rules Committee
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 242)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Science and Astronautics (3 folders)
    - Science and Astronautics--Apollo 11
    - Science and Astronautics--Apollo 11 Pictures (2 folders)
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 243)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Science and Astronautics--Downing Amendment (Noise Reduction Lab)
    - Science and Astronautics--National Institutional Grants Program
    - Science and Astronautics--Oversight Subcommittee
    - Science and Astronautics--Space and Applications Subcommittee (2 folders)
    - Standards of Official Conduct
    - Veterans Affairs Committee
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 244)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Ways and Means Committee
    - Ways and Means Committee--Chamberlain Bill (H.R. 1017)
    - Ways and Means Committee--Family Assistance Program (H.R. 16311)
    - Ways and Means Committee--800 Experiment
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 245)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Ways and Means Committee--Comprehensive Income Maintenance
    - Ways and Means Committee--Social Security--Medicare
    - Ways and Means Committee--Extend Surtax and Investment Credit Appeal
    - Ways and Means Committee--Tax Reform (2 folders)
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 246)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Ways and Means Committee--Tax Reform (4 folders)
    - Ways and Means Committee--Tax Reform--Municipal Bonds
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 247)
  - Committees [and General Legislation].
    - Ways and Means Committee--Colonial Williamsburg--Tax Exempt Status
  - Federal Installations.
    - Assateague National Seashore (2 folders)
    - Back Bay Wildlife Refuge
    - Barrier Islands of Virginia--Eastern Shore
    - Cape Henry Memorial
    - Cape Henry Weather Station
    - Camp Peary--Experimental Training Activity
    - Camp Pendleton
    - Cheatham Annex
    - Coast Guard Reserve Training Center--Yorktown Station/s
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 248)
  - Federal Installations.
    - Colonial National Historical Park--Yorktown
    - Continental Army Command (CONARC)--Hotel Chamberlin
    - Fort Eustis--General
    - Fort Eustis--AAVLABS
    - Fort Monroe--General
    - Fort Monroe--Civilian Parking Areas
    - Fort Story
    - Langley Air Force Base
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 249)
  - Federal Installations.
    - Little Creek Amphibious Base
    - NASA--Langley AFB
    - NASA--Space Radiation Effects Laboratory
    - NASA--Wallops Island
    - Naval Air Rework Facility [NARF]
    - Naval Air Station Norfolk
    - Naval Air Station Oceana
    - Navy Public Works Center
    - Norfolk Naval Shipyard--General
    - Norfolk Naval Shipyard--Supervisor's Wages--Federal Wage Survey
    - Norfolk Naval Shipyard--Personnel Problem
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 250)
  - Federal Installations.
    - Norfolk Naval Supply Center--Reduction in Force--Mr. Powers
    - Portsmouth Naval Hospital
    - Virginia Beach Coast Guard Station
    - VA Center--Hampton
    - Yorktown Naval Weapons Station
    - Yorktown Colonial National Historical Park
  - General Files.
    - Accomack County
    - Accomplishments
    - Adams Island/Fisherman's Island
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 251)
  - General Files.
    - Department of Agriculture (2 folders)
    - Department of the Air Force--General
    - Department of the Air Force--Prime Beef
    - Andrews Home for the Aged, Inc.
    - Anheuser-Busch 55
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 252)
  - General Files.
    - American World Trade Ship SS Atlantic
    - Answerphone
    - Appointments
    - Department of the Army--General
    - Department of the Army--National Cemeteries
    - Army and Air Force Exchange Service
    - Army Corps of Engineers--Water Resources Council
    - Atomic Energy Commission [AEC]
    - A--General
    - Basic Construction
    - Books
    - Bureau of the Budget
    - Bureau of Commercial Fisheries
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 253)
  - General Files.
    - B--General
    - Campus Disorders
    - Cape Hatteras
    - Cards
    - Census
    - Chesapeake Bay
    - Chesapeake Bay Authority
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 254)
  - General Files.
    - Chesapeake Bay Seafood Industry--General Tunner (2 folders)
    - Chincoteague
    - Christopher Newport College
    - Civil Aeronautics Board [CAB]
    - U.S. Commission on Civil Rights
    - Civil Service Commission
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 255)
  - General Files.
    - Coast Guard--General
    - Coast Guard--Fifth Coast Guard District
    - Coast Guard--Yancey Disaster--Chesapeake Bay Bridge Tunnel
    - Coastal Plains Regional Council
    - College Admissions
    - Department of Commerce
    - Communism
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 256)
  - General Files.
    - Congratulations
    - Cultural Affairs
    - Customs
    - C--General
    - Davenport, Jack--Urea Barter, Offer #10
    - Department of Defense
    - Department of Defense--ABM
    - Defense Supply Agency--Consolidation, Richmond-New York
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 257)
  - General Files.
    - DeMolay
    - D--General
    - Eastern Shore of Virginia
    - Eastern State Hospital
    - Eastern Virginia Medical School Foundation
    - Economic Development Administration
    - Environment
    - Exmore
    - Expo '770
    - E--General
    - Federal Aviation Administration [FAA]
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation [FBI]
    - Federal Communications Commission [FCC]--General
    - Federal Communications Commission [FCC]--Agnew Speech
    - Federal Highway Administration
    - Federal Power Commission--General
    - Federal Power Commission--Fuel Shortage
- 91st Congress, 1969-1970. (Box 258)